Heat. Heat.
Heat. Heat. N.
[Music]
Hello, good evening, good day everybody
and welcome to this special emergency
episode. We are discussing Nepal today.
I hope everyone's doing great. Let me
see quickly who all is there on the live
chat. I can see Shashank Shivas the
might is right. Nishal Radhimir Putin
Suman Shaker Sarangi Iatistic Poor Man
Aush Singh Patriotic Itachi Space
Abinhat Achara Shashank Shivastav
Chaitanya Manjul Manuja Ram Shukla from
Kpur Shashank Shivastav
Arrow 14. Who else? Subramanyam Swami is
here. Well, and it is hensy penguin
actually dyank
sarbari das Gupta satellite
chowi tushar kalborgi
tatagat karan Richard artist Boston
bread mlavin hello js aeri navin nav
kishadwa sang from dargilling hello
Arjun a rishikesh zag mo dak hello
rahachandraanveda
anand vajantri deepikar rohan parik
Vikash PJ Gravity Kahi the Indian and
everybody else. All right, good to see
you all. Thank you so much for being on
the live chat and let us see what
questions we have. I'll take as many
questions as possible.
Let's begin with this by Aayush Singh.
Aush Singh says, let us uh begin from
the basics.
Please explain the series of events that
took place in Nepal. What's the current
status? What are the scenarios for the
for the upcoming future?
Okay, let's begin from the basics.
Nepal was founded in the 1700s.
You want to begin from the basics?
Uh
uh okay, we're going to not go to to the
entire history of Nepal. Okay. Uh so
past 30 or so years okay there there was
the regime change operation in Nepal. Uh
there was in the 1990s there was this
Mauist insurgency
in Nepal
and
one of the former retired
heads of RAW
India's RAW I think it was Mr. Dulat or
somebody I don't remember who it was but
he had said much later that India the
government of India at that time
supported the Maoists
and as a consequence the the monarchy of
Nepal was overthrown. Eventually the
royal family was wiped out in a very
mysterious occurrence one night and ever
since that time the Mauists had have
been running Nepal.
So why would an Indian government
support the Mauist who are pro-china?
Beats me.
It's like asking why did Mr. Neu do so
and so things? Why did he give away uh
the Cabo Valley of Manipur to Burma? Why
did he give away Guadada to Pakistan and
so on? There's no explanation. There's
no rational logical explanation. So the
Indian prime minister of the time
supported the Mauist insurgency against
the the Nepalese monarchy. As a result,
the Maoists won and they were pro-China,
not pro- India. So India supported a
pro-China uh insurgency.
And the Mauists said that their their
demand was that their claim was that the
Nepalese monarchy was very corrupt. It
was exploiting the people blah blah blah
all that. So we will come to power and
we will clean everything up. That's what
they had claimed. So the Mauists came to
power and what did they do? 30 years of
even more corruption than what they
claimed was happening with the with the
monarchy. Super super corruption
revolving door president prime
ministership and and so on. And the
Nepalese people were taken for granted
and they were taken for a ride. So
eventually
the people of Nepal obviously were
suffering and they could see that the
Nepalese politicians were enjoying
themselves. They're fattening themselves
at the expense of the Nepalese taxpayer.
their families are living abroad and so
all this was exposed on social media by
various Nepalese youngsters I suppose
and because all the Nepalese politicians
their real their you know secrets were
being exposed their luxurious lives and
all that without any source of income h
all that was being exposed on social
media that's the media so they banned
social media
and because of that um young people in
Nepal who are hooked to social media all
day doing scrolling reels They got upset
and they went in the streets and that is
what they call a Gen Z revolt.
Now, so it is being said that this is a
Gen Z revolt. Gen Z and the Jenzi are
upset with corruption. So if they are
upset with corruption, why did people
try and attack the Pashupatin temple?
What does the Pashupatin temple have to
do with corruption in Nepal? H why were
other temples attacked?
There is video footage of people trying
to climb the fence to climb the gates of
Pashupatin temple. It was thwarted. The
attempt was thwarted but there was an
attempt to vandalize the Pashupatin
temple. The most historic temple in
Nepal, Lord Shiva temple. Why would you
do that? If you have a problem with
corruption.
Okay. So the the Jenzi protest starts.
Then some pol some policeman in Nepal,
some police officer who has family in
the US, he orders his police uh boys to
to open fire on students.
Hm.
So apparently some students died
tragically. And when something like this
happens, even if it's a protest that has
nothing to do with the common people's
aspirations, when innocent students are
killed, everybody gets angry and then
more people get involved in the protest
just out of anger. He killed an innocent
student and that's when opportunistic
forces can hijack
the protests. Okay.
So now it becomes clear that there are
various people who are apparently being
projected as the next prime minister of
Nepal. There is some rapper who is the
mayor of Kmando a very very virudently
anti-India guy.
Okay. Um he was in bed with the Chinese
Communist Party formerly
and now he's in bed with the American
ambassador
figuratively or whatever. Hm. So there
is that. Then there is this uh Hami
Nepal NGO whose uh whose boss or whose
head or co-founder or whatever this
Gurong person I forget his first name.
This gentleman he's not Jenzi he's in
his 30s and he has ties with foreign
funders. His organization gets lots of
funding from other other countries. You
can guess which countries it will be and
so on. So there are all these forces,
all these things that are now coming up.
There is some arms dealer who is also
funding something or the other. So the
point is that it started with something
legitimate possibly. Gen Z was upset,
the students were upset and then it
devolved into chaos and then
opportunistic forces hijacked this
thing. They attacked the Supreme Court
of Nepal. They burned the whole Supreme
Court. People who had cases pending for
God knows how many years. they will
never get justice now. Yeah. Is that how
you end corruption?
Is that how you end corruption? By
attacking temples, you you got to end
corruption.
And then obviously uh the houses of
various politicians have been attacked
and some have been burned and God knows
what happened. Some kind of violence.
Some people may have lost their lives
and and that sort of thing. So this has
nothing anymore to do with Jenzi. the
people who are now being projected as
the next leader of leaders or leaders of
of Nepal, they all have ties with the
United States.
Okay. And Anurag is saying that
Christian missionaries attacked
Pashupatina temple and this Yeah. Okay.
And this so-called Deependra Deependran
or whatever his name is this mayor of
Kathmandu, this fellow, he is a
proponent of greater Nepal. He wants
Indian territory to be part of Nepal.
Yeah. So this is the situation right
now. This is a classic
regime change operation. This is a
classic color revolution situation and
the Americans have perfected this. They
have done this over and over again in so
many countries. It started with the
poppy revolution and the tulip
revolution and whatnot in the early
2000s in Central Asia
places like Kyrgystan and whatnot.
Yeah. Balendra du du. Thank you.
Balendrasha.
Balendra is that mayor of of Katwando.
So this is another color revolution.
So that's the current status. Right now
it is chaos. It is still chaos. There is
still all the dust in the air. So so to
say in the next few days things will
become more clear who is now going to be
projected as the next leader of Nepal.
And
in case what I am saying is correct that
the US is behind this then in the next
few days you will see
a US puppet coming to power in Nepal.
Some young person who has connections
with the US
either some exjustice of Supreme Court
very easy to see connections there or
some rapper or some former news anchor
or some NGO person.
So that is the situation. So what is
going to happen now? What is going to
happen in the future? That's what is
going to happen. The moment we see who
is now being projected as the next next
prime minister and who is placed as the
next prime minister of Nepal, that will
clarify everything.
This is not some this this started as
something that was genuine. The students
were frustrated sure but it has been
taken in a totally different direction
and this is now a regime change
operation. And who does it affect? That
also we'll discuss. Who does it affect?
Does it affect India? Does it affect
China? Well, KP Sharma Ooli was very
pro-China, very anti-India. So, this is
a setback to China because he was
China's agent. The prime minister of
Nepal was a Chinese agent. He has been
ousted. Now there's a US agent who is
going to be in power. So, you see who
suffers at the end of the day. My dear
Nepali people, you suffer.
No matter who is in power, he's always
the agent of some somebody else. Who is
going to be your agent? The people of
Nepal, you also should have an agent,
right?
So this is going to solve nothing for
Nepal.
When you have a prime minister or a
leader of the country who serves a
foreign power, you people,
you're going to suffer. Nothing will
change for you. Nothing.
And this prayer, who is this pria?
This prayer is saying that whatever
happens in Nepal happens at the behest
of raw. Don't spread rumors. Sorry, I'm
going to have to remove you from this
channel. I don't need people like you
here.
So see perhaps this penna person is a
Nepalese person and you can see how much
virulent hate there is for India today
in Nepal. Why is it like this? It's
because people have been brainwashed in
Nepal. These Mao has so been in power
for 30 years, 30 plus years. They have
been brainwashing the people into
believing that India is the enemy
because they have been serving China.
The Mauists have been serving China. So
they have been brainwashing people from
the from a very young age that India is
the enemy. India is the nation that has
been oppressing Nepal for for god knows
whatever time right so young people are
misled and they have this hatred for
India. If you see comments on social
media, Nepalese citizens, many of them,
not I'm sure not all of them, many of
them have the same hatred for India that
Pakistanis have. The only difference is
that there is no religious angle there.
So that's the situation. India has
mishandled the Nepal situation the past
30 years. In 2015, the why was there a
need to do a blockade of Nepal?
So Indian politicians are also to blame
for this situation.
Uh and yeah, so that's where we are.
Okay, now we'll take some more
questions.
Um,
Heny Penguin says that Sushila Ki
doesn't seem to be a stood. The sto
seems to be Balin. Balin is a clearly a
student. See this Balin guy, the mayor
of Kathmandu, he was like I said slight
somewhat inappropriately perhaps. He was
in bed with the Chinese. H he was a
Chinese agent. What does it mean that he
he was a Chinese agent? It means that he
was getting money from the Chinese. The
Chinese were paying him to be their
agent. Now you can say that he has been
visited by the American ambassador and
now he is friends with the Americans.
What does it mean? This guy is up for
sale. Whoever pays more, he will work
for them. That's the kind of guy this
bal person is. You think he will work
for the people of Nepal?
Whoever gives more money, it's like an
IPL auction.
This guy here here is up for sale. Who
is willing to pay more? He will work for
them. He's a freelancer.
Okay. So Balin clearly Balin is is is a
stoogge.
He is not working for the interests of
Nepal. What you want? Forget about
India. Let's say Nepal has a problem
with India. That's your that's entirely
your your matter. You are a sovereign
nation and you can have a problem with
whoever you feel like. It's it's
entirely your choice. But what's
important is that whoever is your
leader, that person should serve you,
your country and your people. You should
not serve a foreign power.
Nepales like to say a they keep saying
that you know we never came under the
British oppression occupation. We never
came under the East India Company. We
were never under the British Raj. Well,
what is this happening right now? Your
politicians are serving foreign masters.
Ours are not today. You see the
difference? So Balin is a stoogge. No
question. I don't know about Sushi Kark.
I haven't I haven't looked into her
anticedants.
We will see about that. We'll see.
Vladimir Putin says many liberals were
demanding these protests in India also.
They have already brainwashed some
people on X. What should the Indian
government do with these individuals?
I'll tell you why is it so easy to
brainwash people? Because the entire
education system is controlled by these
liberals,
our entire education system is
controlled by them. If you look at
higher education, if you look at
colleges, universities, if you look at
something like the Tata Institute of
Social Sciences, do you know how how
anti-India it is? Do you know all the
IIT departments of humanities? How
anti-India they are? How Hindu they are?
When you have when you have professors
and teachers like these who teach
children, children are impressionable.
When you are 15, 16, 18, 20, 25, you're
impressionable. When somebody with
authority teaches you something and says
that India is an oppressive state,
you'll believe it.
That's how they are making young pliable
people the Gen Z they are making them
the canon foder for these revolutions
anti-India revolutions right that is
what's being done so these people
they've already grown up through the
education system they already believe
all these things and when you start this
movement on social media on X or
whatever they will go and sign up for
being soldiers so what should the
government and then you have these
liberals who are these liberals
These are aspiring Zalinskis.
See this Balin guy is a Nepal is
aspiring Zalinski. H he's an aspiring
Zalinski from Nepal. There are plenty of
aspiring Zilinskis in India at very high
positions, lower positions etc etc etc.
These are your liberals.
They have they are not liberal by any
means. They just said that I am liberal
which means I am anti-India,
anti-government, anti-ivilization and I
will being liberal means you are on
somebody's payroll essentially in India
that's what it means when somebody says
I'm liberal it means I am either on
someone on a foreign country's payroll
or I want to be on a foreign country's
payroll I'm an aspiring zalinski
that's what it means what should the
government of India do about this keep a
watch on these people and keep track of
where the money comes from how much
money is coming in where is it going
keep track of everything and if if
something nefarious is is is attempted
clamp down on it that's what I would say
law and order
right
uh
Boston okay we're not discussing listen
we discussing Nepal today please please
let's not go here and there and
everywhere we're discussing Nepal
D shukla says do you think Nepal will
become Hindu Russia right now it's
becoming a American vasal
right now that's the situation.
Hinduashtra, what Hinduashtra
becoming an American vasal right now.
Uh can Bhutan be the next target? We'll
have to see about that. McLean says all
of our neighbors had regime change in
the last 5 years. Is something big
coming from us? And now this this is an
important question. What's happened in
the past five or so years?
In 2022, you had the first regime change
operation. Uh
there was west Pakistan Imran Khan who
was pro-China was ousted and this Sharif
fellow this little Sharif guy this much
he came to he was put in the hot seat
obviously the army is running the show
but Sharif is put in the hot seat and
he's an American stoogge
uh he also tries to meet Xiinping and go
to Beijing or Tanjin or whatever but
he's an American stoogge so the first
regime change operation happens there in
2022 in West Pakistan Pakistan. Then
last year there was a regime change
operation in Bangladesh which turned
Bangladesh into East Pakistan.
Okay. So there's a regime change
operation in Bangladesh and uh Shazin is
ousted and this Muhammad Yunus, this
little Muhammad Inus, he's put in the
hot seat and the army is running the
show. Now there's Nepal. In Nepal also
we're going to have some Balain or some
some whoever it is is going to put into
into the hot seat and that person will
serve the US agenda again. So you know
what's happening? India is being ring
fenced.
We our our great strategic experts, they
like to talk about the Chinese string of
pearls, right? Well, the real issue is
not the Chinese string of pearls. It is
the American ring of thorns,
fence of thorns the Americans are
building around India, East Pakistan,
West Pakistan, Nepal. Uh the Taliban are
also on the American payroll. Even
though Taliban are positively inclined
towards India, then they will try Maldi.
They'll try
Bangladesh there's also there's also
Myanmar going on Myanmar this is civil
war in Myanmar project Kukiland for
Christ who started that the US started
that so so all of that they are
encircling India they are their
objective is to contain India and they
may attempt a regime change operation in
India in the coming weeks or months
Bidori says shouldn't India fast
we discussing sir we discussing Nepal
today
Shankar Vik says is uh do you think
India have not pursued a strong
strategic military or economic alliance
with Nepal back in the early thousand
2000s knowing full well the Chinese
intent? Listen
in the 1990s the Mauists it was known
were a communist guerrilla force. They
were funded by China.
And yet the Indian prime minister of
that time, whoever he was,
he supported the Maoist insurgency
against the Hindu Rajantra of Nepal.
And because of Indian support more than
Chinese support, the Maoist terrorists
won. This Pratunda fellow, he used to be
a Mauist terrorist.
So India itself pushed Nepal into the
arms of the Mauists.
H not today's India that India and that
prime minister that fellow
whoever it was right that is what
happened now in the 2000s we had who did
we have who would until 2004 we had Mr.
Wajpay's government I'm not sure what
Mr. Wajp's foreign policy was okay I am
not very clear about that um and then we
had the 10 years of Dr. Manm Singh what
was the 10 years of Dr. Dr. Man Singh do
you think that they were pursuing uh
national interest prioritizing policies
in India during the 10 years of Dr. mon
Singh do you think the national interest
was prioritized do you think India's
foreign policy was robust do you think
India's defense policy was robust
nothing was robust
it is alleged
it is alleged that India was up for sale
at the time alleged alleged alleged okay
so yeah India did not pursue the right
policy with Nepal in the 2000s
the government of India knew exactly
what the Chinese were doing no nothing
even in the 2010s what kind of policy
would be would you pursue with Nepal I
don't know what so yeah there we have it
u Akar says Nepal has become a hub for
ISI CIA and Chinese agents becoming a
liability from a hyper realist lens it
would be prudent for India to have Nepal
merge into India like Kim did
I think it it will be better if Nepal
remains a sovereign nation I'll tell you
And obviously Nepal should not be under
the goddamn Maoists, these terrorists.
Nepal ideally should be a Hindu
Rajantra. But it will be better for
Nepal if it stays a sovereign nation
with the same relationship that we have
currently open borders and same people.
Why? Because the moment Nepal is
absorbed into India, it comes under
secularism and then you will have a
million Bangladeshes entering Nepal. You
will have a million Christian
missionaries entering Nepal in Nepal
will be ruined. Whatever little culture
they've been able to preserve Hindu
culture I think it'll be good if if it
if if it remains if it is preserved
instead of coming under sec Indian
secularism Indians I'll tell you what
India is the world's most hindophobic
nation you people may not realize it
because Indians we we live in La La Land
Hindus have more rights in the United
States than in India Hindus have more
rights in equal rights in Europe than in
India
Okay, India is the world's most Hindu
phobic country.
Hindus have more rights outside of India
than inside India. You want the same
thing to happen to Nepal.
Your constitution discriminates against
you Hindus. Your laws discriminate
against you. Your government policies
discriminate against you, but you people
don't realize it because you're goddamn
blind, right?
So, do we want that to happen to Nepal?
Do we want a million Bangladeshes in
Nepal?
Do you want uh churches coming up all
over Nepal in in place of Hindu temples?
H I don't want that.
I think it'll be good if Nepal remains a
sovereign nation with robust excellent
civilizational and and overall ties with
India and ideally it should be a Hindu
Raj tantra not a goddess ma godamn
maestinfested hell hole that's that's
what will be good for Nepal.
Uh Pratt Dhana says India and China look
helpless against American regime change
and operations. Why is that? Because the
Americans have perfected how to do this.
And see
the the way things are right now. See if
you have a nation that is your friend
and a regime change operation is
attempted there. Well, historically you
would have simply sent your army and
ended this nonsense. But today if you
send your army then the entire
international community will condemn you
and impose sanctions on you that you are
interfering in the sovereign affairs of
in the internal affairs of a sovereign
nation. So you can't do anything because
otherwise you'll face all these
consequences. Uh the Chinese
the Chinese also can't do a thing as you
can see because right now it is a
pro-China government that has been
dismantled. What are the Chinese doing?
Staying out of it. They're waiting and
watching. They also have a common
border. The Tibet Nepal border is there,
right? Chinese aren't doing anything.
The Americans are so powerful. People
don't realize how powerful the Americans
are.
Look at Taiwan.
Look at Taiwan. It's It's in China's
backyard. What does China desire more
than anything else? More than anything
else, China desires Taiwan. Taiwan is in
China's backyard. China has a the
world's largest navy. China has
extremely modern armed forces allegedly.
So why isn't China taking Taiwan?
Because the Americans are so powerful
that even in China's backyard, China
can't take Taiwan. People don't realize
how powerful the Americans are.
So that's the situation. If India or
China attempt, let's say hypothetically
India attempts to intervene in Nepal and
oust all these foreign forces,
the Americans and the and the EU and the
so-called international community will
immediately impose all kinds of
sanctions on India.
India will be condemned in the UN
security council. India will be
portrayed as an aggressor the way Putin
is ported as an aggressor and so much
more. India will be vilified.
It'll hurt India very badly. That's why
India stays out of this.
Forget about all of that. Look at
Manipur.
What's happening in Manipur? An invasion
by cookies. Is India doing anything
about it? The moment you take action
against these terrorists who have come
with women and children, the the world
will say that India is violating human
rights of its own citizens. Even though
cookies are not our people,
even in our own territory,
right? India is is right now ho how when
was the last time the prime minister
went to Manipur why is he staying out of
it why has he not spoken about Manipur
his hands are tied you see that's how
powerful the Americans are forget about
Nepal in India itself we have problems
we have industrial scale Christian
conversion happening across India what
is the government of India doing the
moment the government of India tries to
stop it India will be labeled as a
nation that that lacks religious freedom
and all kinds uh various actions will be
taken against India.
So this is how these people operate the
Americans. They try to destroy
civilization. So India and China are
currently when it comes to Nepal at
least we are helpless. We're staying out
of it.
Shasah. Well, thank you so much sir.
That's so kind of you. Thank you.
No sir. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Taran Tapa says, "Time for a separate
North Bengal state for national security
concern." North Bengal. Why North
Bengal?
I'm not sure what you're referring to.
I'm looking at the map here. North
Bengal.
North of Bengal. You have
Yeah, you have beh.
Okay. So now further questions
uh Amisha G today we'll discuss Nepal.
We'll we can take these questions on the
weekend.
Uh
okay Amisha is asking what is India's
official stand on the Nepal situation?
Uh should we close our borders with
Nepal as of now? Right now right now
what is the stand? I think the prime
minister of India Mr. Modi he had
tweeted I think yesterday or day before
yesterday that whatever is happening is
terrible. the violence it needs to end
and beyond that we have said nothing. So
our official stand right now is that we
will stay out of it. We'll wait and
watch. We'll wait and watch. That is our
stand. Uh see generally when these
things happen the government of India
maintains extreme calm.
It uh its statements are very mature,
very restrained. behind the scenes maybe
we may be doing something perhaps uh but
uh officially we'll be very restrained
and very mature and we'll urge for calm
we'll urge for peace we'll urge for
quiet we'll urge for a peaceful
resolution to whatever issues are
existing and whatever has developed
that's what we would say should we close
our borders with Nepal as of now uh it's
something that could be on the table
perhaps depending on how things go um
we'll have to close borders only in very
specific situations So if there is a
huge influx of people coming from Nepal
in case there is a tremendous amount of
violence and people are fleeing Nepal
and millions of people want to come into
India suddenly that would be a problem
but right now I don't think there's any
need for the government of India to
close the borders unless there's a
situation where the ISI is pushing in
terrorists from Nepal or something and
that sort of thing has kind of happened
in the past but uh right now I think
there's no need to close the borders uh
we will obviously reassess the situation
once the new leader puppet leader of
Nepal will be announced and then we'll
see what their stance is towards India
whether they are being uh hostile
whether they are being friendly what is
their stand and then we'll have to see
how how how things go because see the
thing is that Nepal in India we have an
open border as everyone knows and the
people of Nepal can come to India
without a visa no need for a visa they
can live in India they can work in in
India just like Indians they're treated
essentially just like Indian citizens
except for the fact that they and vote.
Um I'm sure there are some other
restrictions also but otherwise we the
we are the same right and the most
important thing is that Nepali citizens
can serve in the Indian armed forces
just like Indian citizens. Uh so if now
there's a pro- US regime in Nepal okay
and they have a very strongly anti-India
stance and we'll have to be very careful
about all these things. So we'll have to
see going forward how it is. Right now
we wait and watch and we reassess after
a while. S ready says he means darling.
In that case I understand. Sure.
Poor man says Nepal, Myanmar,
Bangladesh, Pakistan, everywhere the
same story. Can they try the same in
India? Maybe not regime change but
regime degrade. Look, I'll tell you
what.
You're right. We are being encircled a
fence of thorns around India. An
American fence of thorns. East Pakistan,
West Pakistan, U Myanmar, now Nepal,
four countries, four of our neighboring
countries uh and and Myanmar is in civil
war and it's spilling over into Manipur.
Manipur is is a crisis. Manipur is an
invasion by foreign foreign squatters
into India and those foreign squatters
in India in Manipur they have no
allegiance to our culture, civilization,
history or country. Even if they have
other cards, it's a big problem. Now we
have Nepal. So the question that poor
man is asking is can they try the same
thing in India? Maybe not regime change,
but maybe a regime degrade.
So
look, first of all, understand this. The
Americans don't like Prime Minister
Modi.
He's the only world leader who has stood
up to the US. Ever since Trump unleashed
his war of terror on the world, economic
war of terror, the the the the tariffs,
the war of tariffs on the world, only
one country has stood up to the US. It's
India. Everybody else has negotiated it.
We also try to negotiate. Okay. But the
demands the Americans made were
unacceptable.
So today the media is saying that you
know Mr. Modi is being very obstinate.
He's being very egoistic. Just bow down
to Mr. Trump a little bit. Nominate him
for a Nobel Prize. Accept that Trump has
some had some some some participation in
the in the park the ceasefire with
Pakistan. Accept these things and
everything will be fine. That's it.
What's what what is the truth really?
What is the truth? The truth is that the
Americans want India to open up the
entire market to American goods,
including the agriculture sector,
including the dairy sector. If we open
that up, all our industries will die.
Everybody will be out of a job and we
will be a vasal state. So we are saying
no and we we are not accept agreeing to
this and that's why the Americans are
deeply unhappy with Mr. Modi. They know
that if somebody else whoever whoever
that may be whoever they know Americans
know that if somebody else comes to
power one of their preferred politicians
then India will be very happy to
immediately become vasalized.
So America wants a regime change in
India. They want Mr. Modi to go. It is
beneficial for them because they will
gain a very major vasal.
So a military coup is out of the
question in India because a military
coup simply can't work in a country like
India. So what's the other options? The
other option is is a regime change
operation.
So they can try a regime change
operation. They they've been look
they've been playing the game of
subnational diplomacy in India. Uh
aligning with various
regional political parties, hypothetical
regional political parties and so on.
Okay, I'm not naming anybody. There
could be some or the other. whatever it
is, they have been playing this game for
quite some time. The Americans have been
trying to exploit the the the the
divisions that the British created in
society and to to widen the divisions,
to fund various NOS's, to fund various
media outlets, to fund various political
parties, to fund various YouTube
influencers
and fund god knows what else. And the
objective is to create an ecosystem that
will eventually overthrow Modi.
So, they will try their best. I assure
you of that.
regime change or regime degrade? No, not
regime degrade. Regime change. They will
try that in the coming who knows days.
Uh
Udg, thank you so much sir. Thank you.
Adi okay this is nothing to do with
Nepal. So let's not discuss this. Uh
Pranjal Chasi said I are hot beds hot
beds for international professor.
Absolutely right. Absolutely right. I
was expected to write a drama for exam
saying how government mismanaged COVID
lockdowns and paint them in a very
negative light. I tried a mixed
approach. I got bad grades. This is the
problem with the IITs. What is the
government of India doing?
This is the Indian Institutes of what?
Technology, right? Not humanities, not
sociology. This is the Indian Institute
of Technology. Why do you have
humanities departments?
Why that that funding that goes to the
IIT it is earmarked as science funding
but a significant amount of that amount
of that is spent on these humanities
departments
and the humanities departments and the
IITs immediately
I have been saying this for how many
years I have shown on my live streams
the kind of research these IIT
professors are publishing all anti-India
research all hindophobic research cast
this cast that cast oppression India is
a cast cast Just cast cast cast.
Is that what the IITs are supposed to
do?
The government of India is sleeping on
the wheel when it comes to the education
system and these IITs and the humanities
departments. The humanities departments
are snake pit snake pits of leftists.
That's the problem. That's the issue.
Now I'm not saying all I professors are
are like that. I've had an IIT professor
from IIT Mandi
right uh Dr. Dr. Surya Prakashupya who
came on my podcast great guy so he's not
like that
but most of these IIT humanities
departments are snake pits of leftists
so the best thing is stop the humanities
in the IIT this is technology I Indian
institute of technology
they need to end all of this if somebody
wants to learn the humanities go to a
social department somewhere why we join
the IIT we want pure techni we want pure
engineers in societies and if some
students have this desire to to expand
their knowledge and broaden their their
horizons, they can do it in their own
spare time.
India needs to end the humanities
departments in the IITs.
How many times do I have to keep
repeating this? We are digging our own
grave. Big problem. So, Prunal, I'm I'm
I'm grateful to you for for sharing this
personal story of yours.
Sumib Chri well thank you so much sir
um Dvanchkumar says I think Nepal now
may be a military base that the US wants
from us hey we'll see about that yeah
see that could happen so let's wait and
watch let's see how the situation
evolves my assessment is that in the
next few days a new US puppet will come
to power in Nepal
there are many there are many Indian uh
strategic analysts who are saying you
know what that not every not every
revolution is a regime change operation
or a color revolution done by the US. We
need to be more mature in assessing
what's happening in Nepal.
I mean what nonsense.
First of all when something like this
erupts you need to keep quiet for a
couple of days and assess what's
happening. Look at the patterns. Did you
see me tweeting on day one that this is
that this is that no I kept quiet for
two days.
You have to keep quiet for a couple of
days. see the signs, see the patterns,
assess the situation, then open your big
mouth and speak. Right? First two, three
days I was quiet. I did not say a word
about Nepal. Uh but yeah, now it is
clear this is an American mediated
regime change operation. No question
about it. Some people are still saying
no, it's a Jenzi protest. It started as
a Jenzi protest. Now what are the Jenzi
saying? It has nothing to do with us
with us anymore. That's what they are
saying. It's been hijacked by
opportunistic forces, by deeper, more
sinister forces. U so if Nepal in the
next few days sees
uh an American puppet coming to power,
then you may have American military
bases in Nepal. It may happen
very likely in that in that in that
case. Yeah. So then it will be something
that will be used to to potentially
intimidate India as well as China at the
same time. So we'll see.
King Charles says US dist west but still
why western narrative matters.
The western narrative is the US
narrative. It's the US narrative. Okay.
It's not the western narrative. It is
the US narrative. Suspect Jenna says if
the why is the US so successful and why
can't India do such operations? Okay.
How do you do such operations? Tell me
how is the US doing the operations?
They first identify people who are
potential traitors to the country. So if
you want to target Nepal, you look at
people who are already working for
China. H and then you approach them.
Hey, you're working for China. I know, I
understand. Don't worry, I'm not here to
to hurt you. I know you are working for
China. How much are they paying you?
Okay, let's I'm sure you cannot tell me.
So, let me say let me assume that the
Chinese are paying you this much.
Listen, I'll pay you three times the
money. And your sister, I will give her
admission in Harvard. And your nephew,
I'll give him admission in Princeton.
Okay? And your bank balance, we will
have it in London.
So, we'll pay you much more than China.
Don't worry, you work for us. And that's
how they they they identify people and
put them on their payroll. They will
have journalists on their payroll. They
will have uh politicians on their
payroll. They will have mayors on their
payroll. They may have people who work
in certain institutions of the
government on their payroll.
They create a whole network of people
like this. They uh they start NOS's with
with their funding.
To do all this you need very deep
pockets and you need to know how to
identify traitors and and approach them.
Now do does India want to work with
people who are traitors to Nepal
maybe let's say for the sake of
chanakaniti let's work with evil people
for some time okay fine to to achieve a
good objective let us do some let let us
engage temporarily with some bad people
okay maybe now
the problem with this bad people these
traitors is that they the only thing
they want is money and the moment the
Americans or the Chinese come to know
that India is paying this guy this much.
They will double the money. We'll keep
on doubling the money. They have deeper
pockets than India.
See, so you to understand that we we
have limitations.
Our money is to be used for larly bha
yoja right not for all these big things.
So
explore worlds as our next. Okay. Thank
you very much for the fascinating uh
suggestion sir. Thank you.
Okay. Dariling sidi kuri. I get it. I
get it. Okay, I get it. Right. What else
do we have? Uh
Nikesh Dahul says as a Nepali person, I
think we are suffering from exclusionist
policies in since the Neu regime.
Imagine the Gujarati king had succeeded
in other entire other Indian regions
were against Gujarat like like now
Nepal. I understand the perspective of
the Nepalese people completely. The
Nepal the the Nehu government was anti
Nepal.
King Thrian Tribuhan wanted to join
India and and Nehu told him to get lost
and maybe it was a good thing for Nepal
because otherwise Nepal would have been
secularized just like everything else in
India and and then
the government of India in the 1990s
whoever that prime minister was he
unleashed a Mauist terrorist insurgency
on Nepal he he he
aided and abetted that and that's why
you have the Mauist politicians the
super corrupt Maoist politicians who
have been ruling your country for the
past 30 plus years, 30 30-ish years,
right? All thanks to that Indian
government. First it was Neu, then it
was a descendant of Neu who did this. We
also suffered from the same people by
the way. Okay? So I it would be
incorrect for the people of Nepal to
hate Indians.
We have nothing against you. We would
like you to succeed and be happy. It is
certain politicians who have messed up
the whole thing. They messed up things
for Nepal, Indian politicians. But they
messed it up for us also.
We also suffered for decades under the
same politicians. So I don't understand
why Nepal have to hate Indians for that
or India for that. Hate the politicians
who messed everything up. We also hate
them, right? Those magnificent
politicians who did so much harm to us,
to us as well as to you understand.
All right. uh Apurva says how long
before we can start trying the same what
regime change not going to happen you
need very deep pockets for that the
Americans will always have deeper
pockets and what's the point so India
won't be doing that
um
okay Trump says says Makavin Trump said
on truth social he will try to continue
to he will continue to negotiate with
India and Prime Minister Modi finally
responded to him and the then the
protest started in Nepal these things
related everything is related related.
See on the 5th of September Trump had
put on truth social he had put a post on
truth social in which he said that we
have lost India to China and Russia we
have lost India
that was 5th of September what happened
on 6th September next day the protest
started in Nepal clearly it's connected
and the US doesn't like Modi the US is
very upset with Modi that he has dared
to stand up to us. They want Mr. Modi
gone. They want a different leadership
in India. They want some preferred
politician of theirs to be in power in
India. Right? Uh so all of this
encircling of India, the objective is to
destabilize India in the long run. It's
to contain India. It's to prevent India
from growing
by having all these destabilizing
factors all across all around India on
every border.
And if you if you take Nepal then you
can also destabilize China potentially
with that. So it's it's like killing two
birds with one stone. So all of this is
interconnected. All of this.
Madura Majunar Mandal says what should
Barat's ideal strategy be right now
given that all our neighbors are being
controlled by a predatory US? Our
strategy
right now should be to
to
clean up our internal problems
because see you can't control what
happens outside on territory that is not
your sovereign territory. When it comes
to Burma it's not our sovereign
territory and it's being messed up. When
it comes to East Pakistan, West
Pakistan, not our territory. So we can't
control what happens there. Nepal same
thing. So what happens outside of India
we can't control but at least within
India we need to clean up our act. There
are so many problems in India which can
contribute to pro to bigger problems
like regime change.
All of that needs to be looked into.
That's number one. all the traitors who
all the all the aspiring zealinskies
need to be need to be identified and
need to be uh let's say
defanged
in a completely legal transparent
manner. So whatever dubious foreign
funding is flowing into their accounts
from wherever
that needs to be tracked ideally stopped
right confiscate that money
and uh whatever I mean deal with these
people uh as as best appropriate
um secondly all of this uh all of this
funding that's for flowing into India
god what was billions or trillions of
dollars for industrial scale conversions
that needs to end next all the foreign
occupiers of India needs to be thrown
out of India. All the Bangladeshies, the
100 million Bangladeshes and Pakistanis
and cookies and whatnot, throw them out
of India, please. The burden on the
Indian taxpayer will be significantly
reduced. There will be more breathing
space for Indians in India. That needs
to be done. And most importantly, we
need to grow our economy. Whatever it
takes, the economic growth should
continue whichever way. Right? All of
these things we need to do. And of
course take care of border security,
strengthen the armed forces and make
sure that nobody can dare to you know
try any misadventure with us. All of
these things need to be done at this
time at this time when we are encircled.
Look
it may sound like it's a very bad time
for India. The US is against us. But ask
yourself why is the US against us? It's
because we finally matter now.
Imagine if Dr. Manm Singh was still in
power. Do you think the Americans would
be against us? No. They would be very
happy with us. They would have only kept
15% tariffs on us. We would have been
America's good friend because we would
have been a good good little boy. Today
we are not little good little doggy
anymore. We are standing up. The
Americans are they see that as a
problem. So because we are doing well
that's why they are against us. If we
were doing poorly
then nobody would care about us. So
yeah. So there we have it.
geopolitical dub says why didn't the US
set up a military base in Nepal from
their perspective the base would be
useful is it as it contains both India
and China is it because Nepal's it's
because Nepal is landlocked how do you
set up a base in a sovereign country
to it's not like okay I want to build a
construct a building there so I'll go
and construct a building there if it is
not your country if it's a sovereign
country you need permission right from
the
You need permission from the local
government, from the Nepalese
government. Now the Nepalese government
has been a Mauist, a set of Mauist
governments the past 20, 30 years who
have all been in the pocket of China. So
how do you expect the US to get
permission to build a military base
there? Not going to happen, right?
Simple logic. There you have it.
Uh
Chiag says what can these small puppets
being set up around India do to India?
What is their strategic role? Is the
answer to all this just economic growth
and hence military hard power to
control?
What's the purpose of all of these
puppets that you're setting up? Why why
are they doing this? See if they don't
have puppets around India in the
subcontinent then there is no way to
immediately get things done in the
region. So you need puppets. So
initially the the Americans they need a
deal with the Taliban the DHA accord
which has secret clauses and the Taliban
allegedly is being paid a stipend of
between 40 to$100 million in cash every
week by the Americans. So that is one
piece of the p puzzle taken. Okay. It's
it's said. Then 2022 they did Pakistan.
So Pakistan is a US vasal now. Then 24
Bangladesh now Nepal. So you are setting
up all the all the pieces of the
chessboard of the of the jigsaw puzzle
around India. Why? Why do that? What is
the strategic role? Each one of the
pieces of the puzzle has different
strategic roles. Pakistan can unleash
terrorism on India whenever the
Americans tell them to. The Pakistanis
they did terrorism against India for
decades. all funded and financed by the
Americans
and that caused so much trouble to
India. It destabilized Jammu and
Kashmir. It destabilized Punjab. It
caused so much agony and suffering to
the people. It it it lowered our GDP
growth significantly. India was always
on the back foot and so on. So Pakistan
serves that purpose. Pakistan serves the
purpose of nuclear blackmail. Pakistan
if the Americans decide can be turned
into India's Ukraine, a nuclearpowered
Ukraine. So that is the role that
Pakistan plays. Bangladesh or East
Pakistan they can be used to to to push
terrorists into the far east of India
into Manipur, Manipur, Tripura,
uh Misoram. From Tripur and Misoram the
terrorists can be made to come into
Manipur which is the one of the few
Hindu Hindu states left.
Little bit of Hindu people are still
there in Manipur. Apart from Assam, only
Manipur has some Hindus. So we want to
end end Hinduism right? Obviously
Hinduism is evil. So send terrorists
through Bangladesh
into Misoram into Tripura. Have them go
to Manipur and and join forces with the
cookie terrorists. So Bangladesh can
play that role. Bangladesh can keep on
pushing more Bangladeshes into East
Bengal
into West Bengal sorry into West Bengal
and from the West Bengal they can go all
across India even in Jammu. So
Bangladesh can play that destabilizing
role. So you have East Pakistan, West
Pakistan. We understood Taliban they
their objective is to contain China.
That's what that's the deal. And then
you have Nepal. So Nepal by turning that
into US vasal state. Now you can have
Pakistani terrorists fly into Kathmando
then turning into Nepales shaving the
beards and getting a Nepali uh documents
and then walking into India and from
there they can destabilize India or you
can have spies coming into India from
Nepal in the future or maybe you can
have Nepalese
anti-India elements infiltrate the
Indian armed forces because Nepali
citizens can can u can join the Indian
armed forces. You can do so many things.
Do you understand the different roles
each each different strategic roles each
of these assets plays?
So what is the answer to all of this?
The answer to all of this is everlasting
vigilance. Ser vija vigilance. You never
sleep. You always keep your eyes open
and you're always vigilant. And yes,
economic growth and military growth.
Okay.
What else do we have?
Mike is right says whom should I a
Nepalese vote Balain Rabi or Kuman Gish
Singh I think you need to have your
Rajandra back you need to have your king
back
all Balin Balin is a Chinese stoge who
is turned a US stoogge I don't know who
Ramen and G Singh are I'm not sure okay
so I I cannot say about that the best
thing for you is to have your monarchy
back whatever was said about them they
are corrupt blah blah blah they are far
better than the these these these people
that you have day. That is my opinion.
You don't have to take it. I am
obviously not Nepali. So I I can only
put an opinion across. At the end of the
day, it is you people who have to decide
what happens to your country. My simple
suggestion to you is recommendation to
you is you are a sovereign nation. So if
you are a sovereign nation, whoever
leads Nepal has to serve the country and
the people of Nepal, not foreign forces.
This balin fellow, he was a Chinese
agent who is now an American agent. Why
would you vote for a person like that?
Why?
Forget about whether he's anti-India or
not. But he should be pro Nepal at
least.
You need to think critically and
understand which of these politicians is
pro Nepal and which of these is not pro
Nepal. How do you find out?
Look at who is funding them. Look at
their social media. Who are they
meeting? Is he meeting with the US
ambassador?
Is he meeting with Chinese agents? If he
has an organization, NGO, who are the
funders? The funders are listed on the
page, right? Do a little bit of due
diligence.
The moment there is foreign funding, it
is guaranteed that this is a person who
is supported by foreigners, who is
funded by foreigners. And funding is
never free. Nobody gives money for
nothing. If they are getting funding
from abroad, it means they are taking
their orders also. Who should a Nepalese
vote for? You should ideally I would say
vote for your king and get the king back
and get rid of the vote. No more voting.
Okay.
Nishb says, I think we need to wake up
at least in Sri Lanka before something
like this happens in that country. How
do you know something has not happened?
Who is the who who is the rul who's the
prime minister or whatever of of Sri
Lanka right now? President of Sri Lanka.
Uh let's find out, shall we? Let's let's
let's do this together. Okay, let's find
out before something goes wrong in Sri
Lanka. We need to wake up. Let's see who
is
president
of Sri Lanka.
Anura Kumar Danayak.
This is the president of Sri Lanka.
Okay.
So, let's look into this gentleman.
Uh
what are his anticedants?
What does the BBC have to say have to
say about him? A former Marxist. Well,
well, well, well. A former Marxist.
Now, has he does he have any connections
with the World Bank, the IMF, all that?
Okay, I will not do all the research
right now because it will take too much
time. My point is just do a little bit
of searching about the person.
Former Marxist is a huge red flag right
away. Then does he have any connections
with the World Bank, the IMF? Does he
have any relatives who study in the US
or are US citizens or UK citizens? U
does he does he have any residence in a
foreign country? Does he perhaps have a
foreign passport? Does he have bank
accounts in a foreign country? Look into
these things.
Many of these things you'll find out. So
you know
okay
uh let us see.
Ara Mana says if the US CIA deep state
is behind the chaos in Nepal then why
does the US want to topple communist
government which was already anti-India?
At some extent it does add some leverage
for India.
The government was pro-China my friend.
I mean do I have to explain that 2 plus
2 equal to 4 equals to 4? It may have
been an anti-India government but it was
a Chinese it was a pro-China government.
The US wants a government that is both
anti-India and anti-China.
Do you understand? I hope that explains
the situ situation. These Mauists were
all funded by China. They were all
pro-China. That's also a problem for the
US. They want something that is both
anti-India and anti-China. It has to be
only pro- US. That's what they want,
sir.
Okay.
Uh
Koshal Talapati says, "Poli is saying
behind the revolution." Yeah. Uli the
Chinese agent is saying row is behind
this. Yeah, very credible. Thank you.
Pranjal says which why are certain
countries get more prone to getting
destabilized than others? I'll tell you
what, smaller countries are always prone
to being more destabilized. Why do I say
there are only five fully sovereign
nations in the world?
Does it mean that all other nations are
under foreign occupation? No. Just by
the fact that you are so small and such
a small economy and so weak, it
immediately makes you not sovereign
because you are dependent on others for
your basic essentials and necessities.
So that's why small countries,
weak countries with small economies are
always more prone to getting
destabilized because when you are a
small country, when you are a weak
country and if you want to have the same
living standards and amenities as other
countries, then you have to reform
things and for that you need good
politicians. And good politicians
generally come to power saying that
making big promises but they end up
being corrupt like what's happened
happened in Nepal and being corrupt
means you are being you are serving a
foreign power. So you become rich the
politician I if I'm a politician I will
be super rich. I'll have my family
living abroad lots of money lots of
luxury and the poor people of Nepal are
are are all living in poverty and
misery.
So that's the situation right? So that's
why poor countries, smaller countries
are always more prone to being
destabilized because there will be
opportunistic politicians who will be
always ready to always willing to sell
the country for a profit to foreign
biders and so on.
Brunai Kumar says citizens learning
self-defense and energy weapons. Okay.
Sash Jenna says Sri Lanka and Bhutan
next in line until 2019 2029 elections.
I think Bhutan it may not not happen.
Sri Lanka possible. Possible
journey towards inner self says has
Trump helped India by making US clear
never true.
Um has Trump helped India by making it
very clear you can't trust the US? In a
sense it's good. Lots of Indians were of
the opinion that India and US have
shared shared values and we are both
democracies. One is the oldest
democracy, one is the largest democracy.
We are natural partners etc.
Lots of Indians believed this. So this
has come as a wakeup call to see the
true face of the US.
The India US relationship was never
great. Never great. Past 20 years they
have been saying that we have becoming
we have been increasingly becoming
strategic partners. Absolute nonsense.
It was never great.
Okay. Satellite says also stream on
Twitch. I'm streaming on Twitch right
now sir. This is streaming on Twitch.
Yeah, a group or a server. Listen, I
don't have the time to administer a
server. I I am a very busy person. Very
busy. I don't have the time to babysit a
server and appoint and if you appoint
admins then they will start running the
show. I've experienced it before. So
that's why I I know I know I know what
you're saying and I and I I I get it
what you're saying. I know I get it why
you're saying it. Um I I may look into
it perhaps. Yeah, it'll be good to have
a community of like-minded people for
sure. Indeed. Okay. Um
shitis Goyel says any nita who doesn't
achieve 60% if the tasks promised in
manufact should be banned for 10 years
after 4.5 years their performance should
be judged. Well the people need to do it
but the people don't do it. The best way
to do it is through voting. Right? Don't
ban someone for 10 years. Don't vote for
the guy for 10 years. But why are the
people so stupid? Why can't the people
see that the person made a bunch of
promises and they did not fulfill any of
the promises? Why? The people are the
problem in a democracy. You have to
blame the people for keep on keeping on
voting the same corrupt people to power.
Right?
And why does it happen? Why does this
happen? Aren't we a literate country?
Being able to sign your name doesn't
mean literacy when you have no capacity
to think critically. We are not a
literate country.
So the solution is literacy.
Teach people how to think critically.
But that they will never teach because
then the people will become independent.
Right?
Jaganath Vignesh says is the
anti-government uh thing happening in
Indonesia related to Nepal as Indonesia
is close to our upcoming port in India.
It is not related to Nepal. It's a
warning to the government of Indonesia
by the US that I'm not sure what is the
deal. Maybe there is something the
Americans want the government of
Indonesia to do and maybe they're not
doing it. So they have just sent a
warning to the government of Indonesia.
We can topple you anytime.
Do what you told. Stay in line. Don't
get off the reservation, etc. Stay in
your lane. Do as you are told. So this
protest that suddenly happened, it's a
warning to the government.
It's a warning. Similar things have
happened in Thailand also, right? These
things happen. These are all warnings by
the United States to these countries
that we can control what's happening in
your country. We can unleash the
students on demand.
Divor Singh says how were so many people
mobilized so fast. Now this is an
interesting this is an intelligent
question someone is asking. Why doesn't
anyone ask these questions?
Let's say you have a protest that
suddenly happens you know in in some in
some place in some city.
What kind of protest is it? How are so
many mo people mobilized so fast?
Secondly, how do they all have nice
printed banners?
Go to a printer shop, okay, and say that
I want to print a banner that is let's
say 6 ft by 3 ft
and see the quote the printer will give
you. It'll cost you several thousand
rupees.
Now, these people come with hundreds of
banners like these,
all properly printed, all pre-organized.
did not do at the last minute. It was
already. So, they've spent lacks of
rupees printing all the banners,
printing the hats or caps, whatever
slogan is on the hat or cap or whatever,
and getting all these people together.
Everybody has a bottle of water,
everybody gets a meal at a certain time.
How is all this organized? How is
everything organized properly? Who takes
care of the logistics? People simply
don't think they think oh Asab this is
all a popular movement
who is funding everything who is
organizing all this
there is some leadership and some
organization
function going on behind the scenes
hidden away
these students do you think they have
the capacity to mobilize and organize
and and acquire so much money and have
everything printed and organized in in a
short time. No, somebody is doing
everything for them and staying behind
the scenes which means that this is not
a grassroots movement. It's an
astroturfed movements. Right? So, Dn
Singh is asking a great question. He's
expressing skepticism. How is it
possible that such mobilization of such
large numbers of people in such an
organized fashion happen so fast? It
can't happen spontaneously like this.
It's not something that can ever happen
spontaneously. There's always when
something like this happens, there's
always something hidden behind the
scenes.
So maybe it's a foreign embassy or maybe
it is NGO NOS's working on the ground on
behalf of foreign agencies who are
organizing everything and taking care of
all the logistics behind the scenes.
Yeah, that's how it goes.
Pratt Dhana says, "I admire China, but I
love my bat." Well, there's a lot to
admire about China. Yeah. Yeah, I agree.
Sure.
Yeah, DNU Singh sir I I'll not today
we'll only take questions about Nepal.
I'm very sorry but we discussing Nepal
only today. Next time I'll take this.
Please ask next next time. Dorji says uh
well you're very welcome. So thank you.
Uh as an Indian Nepal I'd be pleased to
see more live chats about the Nepal
crisis. Well I hope there is no Nepal
crisis in the future. these emergency uh
sessions they I I only do these when
there's a crisis and the last thing I
want to see is more crisis in Nepal. Uh
but yeah, if this continues
unfortunately then we'll do more more of
this. Sure. So yeah, thank you for the
recommendation sir.
Uh Pratadana says Indonesia joined
breaks that's why sir well also they
Indonesia also was present in the SEO
summit. So there are reasons for these
things you see.
DNU Singh says can we say that this was
the US showing India what they can do
with us as well protests are breaking
out in Assam already
this is no longer a warning to India
this is already a change that the
Americans are making but in a sense you
can say it's a warning because they are
showing to India look we are able to do
this in East Pakistan in west Pakistan
now in Nepal
so you may be next so if you don't want
to be next say yes to all our demands
open up your market to the US
agricultural uh exports and dairy
exports. Vasalize yourself and there
will be no regime change operation in
India. So it's a warning indeed in in a
sense it's a warning to India that we
can take out Nepal, we can take out all
the countries in your in your periphery
next it could be you if you don't want
it agree to our demands. So yeah you
could say it's a warning in a sense. Um
Vom says where will KPI take refuge?
Well as long as he has money he can go
and live in London. London will will
welcome him. London is a city of crooks,
right? London is a city where you have
all kinds of drug dealers and arms
traders and what former terrorists and
former dictators and whatnot who live
there and nice people also. I'm not
saying they're all like that. But the
point is if he has money and I'm sure he
has a tremendous amount of money stolen
from Nepal so he can take refuge in
London. I'm not sure if he will be
welcome in Beijing. I don't think
Beijing has any respect for the guy. a
guy who betrayed his own country even if
he did it for China. But I don't think
Beijing will have any respect for the
guy. So I think KP should go to to to
London. London welcomes everybody anyone
who has money.
Uh satellite says they used Russian oil
to burn buildings. Well well well
uh Dnor Singh says so what's the next
government in Nepal going to look like?
Pakistan 3.0. Um I anticipate that in
the next few days or a couple of weeks
we're going to have a new regime in
Nepal which is going to be either that
former mayor of Kathmandu whatever his
name is who was formerly a Chinese agent
now an American agent or it could be
some some uh former news anchor who was
part of a that prundai government while
already while also being a US citizen
which is completely illegal but he did
that or it could be some Supreme Court
justice that laid
or or it could be somebody else. I don't
know. But whoever comes to power, it's
most likely going to be an American
agent, somebody who works for the US,
not for Nepal. Uh so it's going to be
kind of like Pakistan. See Pak in
Pakistan, you have this Shabbaz Sharif
guy uh who is not really the leader of
Pakistan. He's just the puppet. And
behind him, the real power lies with the
military and the military serves the US.
Right? In Bangladesh, you have this uh
Mohammed Inu fellow, Nobel Prize winner.
He's a puppet. The real power lies in
the hands of the military. The military
serves the US. So in Nepal, you could
have a similar situation. You could have
a puppet face uh a visible face of the
government who will be one of these
individuals and behind the scenes it may
be the army that runs the show. But
whatever happens will be pro- US. So
that's the kind of situation you could
have that you will most likely have in
Nepal in the coming days.
Now these things Bajad says my thoughts
on Kirk death. First of all this is
nothing to do with Nepal. Secondly I was
only vaguely aware of Kirk.
I mean I I I did see some videos of him
here and there but I did not remember
the guy. He's not important from our
perspective. Some American right-wing
politician who got shot. Well, no other
thoughts be beyond that. Divorce says,
"I understand US's power, but I don't
understand how they can almost make
people move like robots in command."
Just money. My my friend sir, Dur sir,
Dnur G. Money,
you have no idea what money does to
people. Money solves all problems.
Every like there are very few problems
that money doesn't solve. It doesn't buy
happiness, but it buys you freedom.
Money solves most problems in the world
and unfortunately everybody has some
price. Almost everybody has some price.
There are very few people who when shown
the money will be able to resist it.
Okay. So not let's let's not blame
people here and there. When when a
sufficient amount of money comes in your
face, you know, I I suppose all your all
your principles fly out of the window.
They can they have essentially unlimited
money. They will give people power.
They'll give people money. They'll give
people prestige.
They'll give people so everything
everything they dreamed of.
So yeah, that's enough to command
people. That's enough to make people do
to to turn people into robots.
And of course, if that doesn't work,
there's always the power of the gun. You
can always have people assassinated,
bumped off. It was an accident. It it
was an accident you see godfather style.
So that's how things are done in the
real world.
Uh
plus ultra says demographic change
reason in Nepal India border. I'm not
aware of any demographic changes in the
border. In the border of Nepal and India
you have the Mad region right the Tari
the Tari region the Madesi people who
are essentially the same people as the
south of the border Bihar Mthila and UP
and all that. Is there a demographic
change that's happening right now? Is
there any large scale industrial scale
Christianization happening? Are there
Bangladeshes coming in? What's the deal?
I'm not sure. I'm not sure.
Um, Dnor Singh says people are
romanticizing this revolution in Nepal.
Is this the best way to look at it?
Making reels with Bollywood songs in the
background. Indians, Indian influencers
are the most low IQ people I've seen.
Most of them.
I mean, just for a few views, you'll do
any nonsense. There is nothing romantic
about this revolution. the so-called
revolution in Nepal. This is a regime
change operation that's going to hurt
Nepal in the long run.
It is like Nepal coming under what it
never came under the East India Company.
Now Nepal is going to come under that.
The past 30 years you've been under the
East China company. Now we will be under
the East US company.
That is what's happening. Is this
something romantic?
This is disaster for Nepal. Your leaders
are serving foreign powers. If they are
serving foreign powers, it means they
they're selling your nation.
And Indians are saying, "Oh, revolution,
jenzi, blah, blah, bollywood songs."
Indians are I don't know what to say. I
mean, I don't I don't want to insult my
own people, but what to say? It's so
frustrating. and and yeah
uh Jagat Vignesh says should our border
stat arm themsel borders
states arm themselves near Nepal and
there's no need to arm ourselves and all
that the Indian defense security forces
etc are more than enough to take care of
any eventualities and I don't I don't
see any any need for any such thing
right now
uh Tanmay says the way the protest was
done it seems The US won't spare anyone
and even their own. You may know about
Charlie Kirk. People here want such
protests also. The US see to understand
why this is the case you have to
understand what the US is. What is the
nature of the United States? People
believe that the US is the world's
oldest democracy.
The US is a two-party system.
The Democrats and the Republicans.
Technically they have some extra other
political parties but realistically they
are immaterial and insignificant. They
don't matter. So for all practical
purposes the US is a two-party system. A
two-party state. A two-party state is
one step above a one party system like
China or North Korea. That's what the US
is. Because whether it's the Republicans
or the Democrats, their foreign policy
is more or less the same. More or less
the same. They'll do regime changes.
Whether it's the Democrats or the
Republicans, they will do regime change
operations. They will do wars. They will
do all that stuff. Makes no difference.
So the US is an autocracy masquerading
as a democracy. The US is an empire.
It's a modern-day empire just like the
Roman Empire used to be, but on a much
larger scale. When you are an empire,
you act in an imperial fashion. You are
imperialistic. And whoever stands in
your way,
they're done. Now people here also want
such protests. Those people are aspiring
Zalinskis.
The people here in India who want such
protests they are aspiring zealinskis
snakes inside the country traitors.
Okay.
Swastik says should India still let
Nepal men in security forces I think a
reassessment will have to be done
depending on what kind of government
comes to power now in Nepal.
Shoubraat Shukla says even if the
leadership is provided from outside why
can't the ground organizers present
inside the territory be contained? How
do they remain hidden? They are not
hidden.
They're not hidden. Everyone knows they
exist. Any NGO
that is funded by foreign foreign
countries is known
but legally they are allowed to operate
right you can't go against the laws of
your own nation.
So in case you have a country like Nepal
for example where the law says that yeah
you can run an NGO with foreign funding
then that law is then weaponized to run
NOS's with foreign funding but the
purpose of the NGOs is to create a
regime change situation but technically
it will say no we are a social NGO we
working for social welfare so all that
documentation will say social welfare
all their activists and and founder and
all that they will have sociological
degrees and they will say that we are
social activists
So on paper everything is perfect. We
this is a social welfare NGO but in
reality they'll be doing something
entirely different. They'll be
mobilizing people to start an armed
revolution or something. So that's how
we do it right very easy. So so legally
if you approach the courts or something
take take the case the courts the courts
will say n what is the problem? This is
perfectly fine perfectly legal.
That's how institutions and laws are
weaponized against countries. Right? So
you will have on on ground organizers
who are openly working and they are
saying we are doing social work social
welfare but actually they are mobilizing
people
they not remain hidden they're out in
the public
divorce I says I used to work in Kirk's
organization wow I understand you won't
take this question Israel probably has
something to do with it I took the
question I don't know about whether is
does Israel something have something to
do with this. I I don't know.
See, I don't remember exactly what Kirk
was doing.
Kirk was a right-wing activist, a
Christian activist. I've seen his wife's
Twitter. All she all she posts is some
Christian quote quotes here and there
all the time. Luke this and Jeremiah
something or the other. All Christian
scriptures she keeps quoting. So super
super Christian people and obviously
very conservative, very right-wing, I'm
sure anti-abortion. And I'm sure that he
called Indians parasites at some point
in time. That's that's all I know about
him. So I don't know if he is pro-ch
Christian etc. Why would Israel want to
kill him off? Uh I I'm not sure about
this. Okay. Yeah. But okay. Well, thank
you for sharing your perspective sir.
Pig and Chad, thank you sir. Very
interesting uh DP you have there.
Uh Ankita is here. Uh what can common
people do to prevent the installation of
some aspiring Zalinski as the prime
minister in such situation? Don't vote
for aspiring Zilinskis. Nothing nothing
more the common people can do beyond
this.
The common people have to be very
responsible in voting. Be don't vote
because you have a gut feeling for
someone. Oh, I like this person. I like
him. He's a very good person. That's
good. I'm glad you have a good feeling
for the person. Now, go and look up the
person. Go and look at all everything
they have done in the past 20 years.
Which organizations have been have they
been associated with? What foreign trips
have they made? What internal trips have
they made? What statements have been
have they been making for the past 20
years? Who are they associated with? How
many bank accounts do they have? What
foreign connections do they have? How
many uh family members do they have who
live abroad or are foreign citizens? And
what countries are these? Look at all
these things. Do your due diligence.
There are always patterns that you will
see with aspiring zillinskies. Okay. So
that's what you do. Beyond that what can
common people do? All you can do is vote
the right way. Divin Singh says should
we buy our own assets in Nepal now may
become a capitalistic heaven. Now I
don't think Nepal will become a
capitalistic heaven even if it becomes a
US vasal.
Uh
outwardly it may become somewhat more
capitalistic. You may have a few more
McDonald's and and and uh and Wendy's
and Burger Kings opening up opening up
in Nepal. Perhaps Pizza Huts and
Dominoes and Taco Bells and Arby's and
whatnot. Yeah, a little bit of that may
happen. Beyond that, it will not become
a capitalistic heaven. If you if you
make the people happy, then there will
be no that is counterproductive. The
people have to be kept downtrodden.
Okay? Especially in a vasal state, don't
make them too happy. it becomes
counterproductive.
uh you need see why do you keep people
unhappy
let's say I am an empire and I have a
vasal a newly minted vasal now should I
give that masal because he has become my
vasal should I give him all the benefits
of the world and should I make his
people super happy well if I make his
people super happy then he will no
longer need me to prop him up his people
themselves will prop him up right I want
him to be vulnerable I want him to have
a sword hanging over his neck all the
time the people may overthrow you. You
are there only because I support you.
But if I make the people prosperous,
they will start supporting him because
they will believe that because because
of him the prosperity has come.
So Nepal will not become a capitalistic
heaven. They will not improve things.
Should we buy our own assets in Nepal
now? Well, if any assets are available,
we can buy them. Yeah.
Sai Kalyan Reddi says if the current
party is pro-right why not taking
straight actions against antinational
elements I feel like both our left and
right are vasals you see
if you take action against
aspiring zalinskis
then the US will say that you are being
politically repressive
democracy is backsliding in India you
there is no political freedom in India
there is No journalistic freedom in
India. You are violating human rights.
You are anti-democratic. Human rights
democracy. Human rights democracy. The
Americans like to keep on harping about
that. They will weaponize that against
you and they can even impose sanctions
on you. Especially if you take any
action against their assets in the
political class in India.
India is full of like I said aspiring
zalinskis,
right? Many of these aspiring zalinskies
could potentially hypothetically be in
various in the political class
hypothetically entirely right we're
talking hypotheticals here. So if there
are hypothetical zilinskies in India who
belong to hypothetical opposition
parties perhaps who knows and if the
government of India takes action against
them
it's going to invite tremendous
repercussions from the US because the US
takes care of their assets. They don't
take care of them because they love
them. They're nice people because
they're assets. The Americans in the
20th century used to say this about
African dictators. They used to say
maybe, yeah, sure, maybe he's a son of a
but he's our son of a
right? He's our asset. So, he may be a
very evil person, but he's our evil guy.
That's why we have to take care of him
because he uh looks out for our
interests. That's how it goes. So, it's
not as simple as okay, this is something
you can do.
It's more complicated than that. So the
Americans if if the government of India
goes against certain NOS's or certain
politicians they will raise hell. It's
going to be more trouble than we than we
want.
RPL says not only Modi versus US but
Canada and China more.
All American was against us in some
shape or form. Canada has has been
weaponized for the past two years.
Right. That fellow what's his name?
Trudeau.
He came to India apparently high on
cocaine and then he alleged that India
had killed some terrorist some Canadian
terrorists in in Canada and then he went
public with all the all these completely
uh baseless claims have which have no no
proof and so on. So Canada has already
been weaponized against India
and uh there there's more obviously
there's more there's more there there
are more nations the US can unleash on
demand against India whenever they think
the time is right
Singh says is our internal security
powerful enough to never let anything
like this happen in India I think the
intern our internal security is pretty
powerful enough but the problem is that
we cannot take action against certain
politicians
if you have seen ever since Mr. Modi
came to power, no politician has been
punished for corruption or for
anti-Indian activities. It's not like
it's because Mr. Modi has a special love
for the political class. It's not that.
It's because these politicians are under
protection from foreign powers and if
you touch them then bad things happen in
a variety of ways inside India, outside
India etc. So you don't want that
trouble. But beyond that the internal
security is pretty robust in India. I
mean the Mauist terrorism that was there
in the the red belt of India the
Chhattisgarh and Jarakhand and all those
areas it's almost disappeared now right
they were all funded by foreign foreign
countries and in they also have the
support of Indian academics and whatnot
and Indian politicians. So that is gone
to a very large extent and uh when it
comes to other other security
areas and so on I think the security has
been has been significantly augmented
and strengthened. So overall I would say
that our intel security is pretty
strong. Is it powerful enough to never
let anything like this happen? That that
depends on political decisions. See in
2019 you had the Dilli riots, the
Shaheenbag uh riots, you had that um
that uh incident in the red fort where
somebody pulled down an Indian flag and
all that. So that was a test of the Modi
government. The security forces could
have neutralized those people very
easily. Laty charge or whatever rubber
bullets. But if somebody gets hurt,
somebody dies for whatever reason,
then that would be the justification of
a much larger scale uprising, right?
Because if somebody dies, the media can
very rapidly go and paint that as an
innocent farmer was killed. Innocent
struggling farmer who came to protect
who came to protest for his rosi roti
was killed by the Modi regime. and then
farmers from from other parts of the
country will get agrieved and they will
join the protest and then you can create
a mass revolution. So the Modi
government was very restrained, very
reserved. They allowed the rampage to
happen. They did not have the armed
forces stopped it stop it and that was a
very wise move. It is only apparent in
retrospect today. But overall the
internal security is powerful enough to
to ensure that nothing really happens.
But when it comes to these critical
critical uh incidents, the political
decisions have to be uh mature.
Subhaari says, "Love for Ben Bengal."
Thank you so much. Do you think uh thank
you very much. Do you think Bengal is
the next Kashmir? After seeing Nepal
regime change, I understand the US can
do anything. Do I think Bengal is the
next Kashmir? It looks like Bengal is
becoming the next Bangladesh.
Not Kashmir but Bangladesh. That's what
it looks like. I mean Bengal this this
lovely beautiful part of India. The
British when they reached Bengal they
said it was the most prosperous part of
India. Of course they had not seen the
whole of India but from their
perspective it was the most prosperous
part of India most fertile and all of
that and Bengali history is such
wonderful history going back how many
thousands of thousands of years. one of
the first one of the earlier examples of
democracy in India. King Shashank
and so much more. But today all all of
that is forgotten Bengal, right? All of
that is forgotten.
And now you have if you I hear that if
you go to Bengali you will find more
Bangladeshes than Bengales. So it looks
like there is a demographic invasion of
Bengal that has happened the past I
don't know how many years. And uh if
this is if something is not done about
this I would say Bengal is doomed to
becoming the next Bangladesh.
Is there a US hand in this? I could be
could be we'll see
DNU Singh says does our vote even make a
difference anymore I think it still does
does make a difference I mean u 2024
votes did make a difference it made the
difference between a stable government
and a coalition government so votes do
make a difference and people should not
take their votes lightly I know it's 1.4
four billion of us. But at the end of
the day, we all have to go out and and
and and put our vote in so that the
right result is
is arrived at.
Uh pagan Chad says, "I witnessed
crypto-christians with my own eyes
subtly influencing the Hindu flance.
Friends, they are leeching all the
benefits of SCST. Who can stop them?" I
think this is something for the
government to do. There's nothing we can
do about this. See, like I've said in so
many times, India is the most
hindophobic country in the world. And
when I mean hindophobic I mean all the
dharmic paths
not just what you call Hinduism.
All the dharmic paths Hindu, Buddhist,
Sik and and Jen. These are the four
major dharmic paths.
We are treated as secondass citizens in
India. There's Hindu apath in India. And
all these people who want to destroy our
culture and civilization they they are
they are protected and and so so and all
that. Who can stop them? government has
to stop them. Let me give you an
example. The British had stolen land
from India, right? We know that they
occupied India for two and a half
centuries. They stole Indian land and
they gave a large amount of land to all
these churches on 99-year leases.
The land was given to the churches on a
99year
lease.
It was not given to the church for free
forever. It was given on lease for 99
years. Those leases have expired today.
The land belongs to the government of
India to the people of India. Why isn't
the government of India taking the land
back from the churches?
What are they scared of? You see how
powerful this mafia is? You see that?
Divor Singh says Nepal was never
colonized. Still they don't see
themselves as a part of India. China's
propaganda must be impressive. It's it's
Chinese propaganda and the brainwashing
imparted on the Nepali citizens by the
Maoists.
See Nepal is not part of India but Nepal
is part of Bharatwash
historic Bharatwash. Nepal was very much
part of it. Before 17 whatever the the
this this kingdom called Nepal did not
exist. It was part of the Lichavi Mahag
Ganatantra
uh Maha Mahajanapada. It was also part
of the Viji Mahajanapada
and it was part of the Kushan Empire. It
was part of the Moria Empire. It was
part of the Gupta Empire. So it's always
been part of Bharat. Since the 1700s, it
became a separate kingdom.
Shri Pratin Aaran Sha was the great king
who established the Nar or Nepal
kingdom, right? The Gora kingdom and
ever since then the British decided that
we will keep this as a as a buffer
state. So Nepal was never part of the
British Raj and uh today's India is kind
of
a fragmented outcome of the British Raj
but Nepal was ever always part of
Batwash but today the people of Nepales
have been brainwashed and they so much
hate has been put into their heads some
of them not all of them that they hate
India just like the Pakistanis do the
only thing is that there's no religious
angle to that u so it's not the Chinese
propaganda it's the Mauists who have
done this this to their people you
injected all this hatred in their minds.
Adityal says how can 20 listen this is
not the day for this we are discussing
Nepal today sir please we'll we'll take
these questions on Saturday
announcement
Saturday I will do a 8 hour live stream
askit
ask me anything I'll take all your
questions 8 hours
okay I know it sounds crazy I'll do that
6 p.m. Saturday I'll put the
announcement up. So Adita I'll take your
question then. Okay. Today we'll discuss
Nepal please. All right. Uh Varelika
says lots of Nepalese people have a
second home. They have bank accounts in
India. There has been and will be a lot
of spillover of Nepalese population.
Don't you think? It depends on how the
regime change proceeds in back home in
Nepal. So if it is a very violent regime
change and lots of people are targeted
for whatever reason. See when a regime
change happens then the new regime often
goes after the people who supported the
old regime
they try to purge the whole society if
that happens then people try to escape
for example what happened let's say in
1971 in East Pakistan
the east the Pakistani government was
was doing a genocide of the Hindus with
American support so when such something
like this happens people have to escape
and where do they escape they go back to
the motherland. So that's why lots of uh
Bangladeshi Hindus came to India and
they settled down in India.
Now absolutely you're right. Lots of
Nepales have second homes and bank
accounts in India. So if there is a
similar situation in Nepal after this
regime change then it will make sense
for them to come and you know settle
down in India. Will there be a lot of
spillover of Nepalese population? It
will certainly be less than the number
of Bangladeshes we have in India.
We have close to around 100 million
illegal Bangladeshi infiltrators all
across the country today in India. So I
think if a few million Nepalese decide
that we want to escape Nepal
hypothetically and settle down in India,
we should welcome them. They are our own
people. And if if that's a burden on the
people of India, get rid of 10 20
million Bangladeshes.
Everything is good. At least the
Nepalese people are culturally and
civilizationally aligned with us unlike
the Bangladeshes. So I would say that
it's it's not necessarily a bad thing.
Nepalese people are wonderful. I've
always had great experiences with
Nepalese people, nicest people in the
world. So that will not be a problem. It
will not be an antiational problem. It
will not be a problem of of cultural and
civilizational strife like what they
have with the goddamn Bangladeshes
illegal infiltrators in India. So get
rid of those. Oh, that's what I would
say. All right.
Uh Vermian Caliber says, "Hope to see
you on Joe Roen podcast someday soon."
All right. Thank you so much.
Divor Singh G says Zalinsky 2.0
imaginary person
let's call him Mr. Z World War Z. If he
manages to gain more seats in 2029, are
we done for? We're done for. We're done.
Cooked. We're done, sir. We're done.
Pratt Dhana says, "One episode on Qatar
Israel thing someday." Okay. If it
becomes something that is notable and
something that um is impactful, I'll be
happy to do it. Sure. Sure.
Uh Jaganath Vignesh says, "Shouldn't we
have a strong lobby in the US and other
western institutions where we change
from their point of view to our POV?"
Basically, the colonized the lobby.
Look, I'll tell you what.
Apparently in the government of India
hired some lobbyist in Washington.
We apparently paid this guy $1.8 million
the last few days. Okay. And now this
guy as as somebody who works for India,
he goes to President Trump and presents
his case and whatever. And then there's
a nice photo opportunity. They're both
smiling. And you know what India's
journalists do? Some utterly imbeilic,
moronic, Indian journalists. I
am using those words deliberately.
I'm not taking anyone's name by the way.
some so-called senior journalists, very
senior journalists and some aspiring
geopolitical experts among journalists,
they went on Twitter and they said
India's lobbyist who India has paid $1.8
million meets Donald Trump.
This is the most behavior I've
ever seen. When you are doing lo when
you hire a lobbyist,
this is supposed to be kept quiet.
You don't announce it. These things are
done behind the scenes, behind the
curtains. You never announce that
somebody is my lobbyist.
But these idiot Indian journalists who
think that they are geopolitical
experts, they went on Twitter and they
started announcing this guy is our
lobbyist. We paid him $1.8 million
because I want to be the first to break
the news, right? I want to be the number
one journalist to help with the Indian
national interest. I should be the one
to break the news. And very prominent
journalists did that. A bunch of utter
idiots who imagine that they are
geopolitical experts.
Let me give them the worst possible
insult I can give them.
Pakistani journalists are better than
this. They have more sense.
Yeah, we should have a strong lobby in
the US. Yeah, we should. But we should
do it quietly. Let let let let us not
allow the idiot journalists to come to
know who who we have hired as lobbyists.
My god, are they traitors or what? Are
they trying to betray India? There are
three options I can think of. Either
they're absolute clueless idiots.
That's number one. Number two, they
don't care about the country. They know
what harm it will do to the country, but
they want to be number one journalist
who broke the news first. Or number
three, they are on some foreign
country's payroll. One of the three
possibilities I most likely they're
idiots
most likely we know what they say never
blame to malice never attribute to
malice what you can attribute to idiocy
or something like that. So these these
senior journalists are a bunch of
idiots. Yeah. And and they think that
they are they're portraying themselves
as geopolitical experts. My god. Divor
Singh says we have our own oligarchs
richest in Asia by the way. We are the
richest guys in the US. Our external
influence does not add up according to
this. Influence is immaterial. Power is
what matters. Let's understand the
difference between influence and power.
Influence is the blue guy here. Power is
the red guy. What's the difference
between influence and power? Let's say I
have a million followers on YouTube, a
million subscribers on YouTube.
It means a million people may sometimes
pay attention to what I say and may
sometimes take it seriously.
H so I have a million subscribers,
million sub subscribers on YouTube and I
have a 200,000 followers on Twitter
which means that those people will
sometimes take me seriously and
sometimes they want to they'll pay
attention to me. That is called
influence.
So it is at their discretion whether to
listen to me or not. Sometimes they
will, sometimes they will not. That is
influence.
Now on the other hand, this guy, red guy
here, he has a hundred men at his
disposal. Those 100 men are armed to the
teeth with the latest weapons and they
will obey him unquestioningly.
Unquestioning obedience. Here I have a
million subscribers. Here I have a 100
guys with unquestioning obedience who
are armed to the teeth. Who is more
powerful? Who will get more done? The
100 guys are worth way more than those
million subscribers.
This million subscribers is influence.
These 100 guys is power. Now imagine you
have a million guys armed to the teeth
with the latest weapons who will obey
you unquestioningly. Imagine the kind of
power that gives you. So when you have
oligarchs and when you have people who
are influential, it makes no difference.
What you need is power. What you need is
assets you can control.
So the influence and soft power blah
blah blah Indians Indians are obsessed
with soft power and influence. Please
wisen up people. Influence make no makes
no difference. Soft power is useless.
What you need is hard power. Power is
what matters not influence.
Uh what happened to Swadzand giving
anti-India state? I have no idea. No
idea. Sorry. Absolutely none. Dimnur
Singh has a lot of questions. If we
hypothetically take over Nepal, what is
America going to do? Admit the pull of a
coup while making us pay for it. They
will never admit the the pull of a coup.
But they will accuse India of invading a
sovereign nation.
They will accuse of India of doing what
Putin did in Ukraine.
That is the deal.
If you hypothetically take over Nepal,
that's what they will say. And there
will have some people in of Nepal's
origin protest in New York in Washington
and in other US other European capitals.
And then the all the western media like
Deutschella like the BBC like the
Guardian like the New York Times like
the Washington Post like 23 whoever
everybody will gang up and create this
huge narrative that India has become
another rogue state like Russia and then
sanctions and destroy the Indian
economy. They will never admit the pull
of a cool. Absolutely not. See that's
how the game is played. Pagan Chad,
thank you so much sir. Thank you. Um DN
Singh says will be taking Nepali
refugees. I might just monopolize your
next two live stream. So much love.
Thank you so much. Um I hope there are
no Nepalese refugees. I hope this new
regime does not target any people any of
their people. But in case there are
people from Nepal who who wish to come
to India while the border is anyway open
they are not refugees. They are our
people. See if if somebody wants to go
from a state to B state in India we
don't call them refugees right. So
similarly if some people from want to
move from Nepal to India well they're
always welcome there will be no no one
stopping them to come in. So there'll be
no issues as such nothing.
Divor Singh says so can the deep pockets
pay off India's top leadership. Now
that's a very interesting question you
ask.
I would say that most politicians most
anywhere in the world. Okay, let's let's
make it a global question. Most
politicians anywhere in the world will
have a certain price.
If the price is low, they will say I
don't do such things. I have standards.
I have principles. But if the price is
high enough, if the right if the right
price is given, they will give in.
But there are some politicians who have
no price and I am firmly convinced Mr.
Modi is one of them. He's one of the
rare politicians who has no price, who
will not be bought out.
So at least when it comes to Mr. Modi,
I'm confident there's no price for him.
He will not sell the country. Others I
don't know. Others I don't know. That's
all I can say. Okay, we'll take a couple
more questions. It's been a pretty long
live stream. Couple more questions. I'll
I'll finish the existing super chats
right and then we'll stop. Uh Roger
Chhatraji says thank you for doing this
on a lighter note. Looking like a Jenzi.
I'm looking like a Jenzi.
Lots of people getting unbrainwashed for
you from you. Well, I I hope so. I don't
want any people to be brainwashed this
way or that way. I want people to be
able to think critically on their own
without needing any help from someone
like me or anybody else. That's that's
all that I that I seek to do. Nothing
else. I don't want to brainwash anyone
but anyway I'm I'm I'm glad that uh at
least some people see sense hopefully.
Yeah. And thank you sir Rajat Gin Singh
says is the if the US is going to fall
eventually are they going to take
everyone down with them?
You know you may have heard of the
Israeli Samson option. The Israeli
Samson option is their nuclear option uh
in which they have a list of targets.
The Samson option is that if Israel goes
down, it'll take everyone down with
them, which means they're enemies.
And a few months ago, some list was
leaked. I'm not sure if it was an
authentic list or list or not, but
apparently there were many major
capitals, world capitals on that list.
So the deal is that if Israel goes down,
if let's say Israel finds itself in a
situation where it's going to be
defeated and it's going to be destroyed
then before the Israel falls they will
launch a massive nuclear strike and
destroy all their enemies before they go
down finally that is the Samson option.
If I go down everyone goes down with me.
Now on the list I saw India was not on
the list of targets but certain very
interesting countries were on the list
of targets. Now that's the Israeli
Samsung option. The US has its own
version of the Samsung option which is a
global Samson option. If the US goes
down the whole world goes down with
them. They will nuke everybody including
nations that have never done a thing to
the US. So the US if it goes down if it
falls they will nuke the entire world.
That's incredibly evil, but that's their
plan.
James, our good old friend is back. Good
to see you, mate. Cheerio, speak about
the Sami people and how we ruined them.
The Sami people have nothing to do with
Nepal. But the Sami people are people
who live in Finland and they are kind of
oppressed. Yeah, I think the the whites
have oppressed the Sami people. Even
though some people themselves look
white, you know, uh blonde hair and blue
eyes and white skin, but I think they
are a finick people or whatever. Um
that's all I can say in very short. But
good to see you, James. Good to see you.
Former colorizer.
All right. Uh
Pagan Chad said, "You predicted a
falling power lashes out." Uh that's
what most falling powers do. Uh they
lash out. So yeah, if the US falls,
it'll lash out at everybody and flatten
the world. Essentially, that's what they
would like to do. Okay, I'm going to end
this live stream here. Thank you so much
everybody for all the questions. I think
we have thrown some clarity on the
situation in Nepal and we will keep an
eye on this. If there are there's more
developments that are potentially
destabilizing or whatever, I shall do
another emergency live stream as and
where when required. So everybody, thank
you so much for all your questions and I
look forward to seeing you on Saturday
when I will do an 8h hour Q&A session. 6
p.m. it starts. It'll go on until 2 2:00
a.m. If ever if the questions last,
we'll do it. I'll be happy to take
repeated questions if required. I look
forward to seeing you there. Those of
you who want to watch my other live,
participate in other liveream, they can
do it at 6 p.m. Until then, take care
everyone. I'll see you soon. Take care.
Keep asking questions. Keep raising your
standards. Thank you everyone. Bye-bye.